quuu.co 2019-12-10

# Quuu - Privacy Policy

Last updated: May 10th 2018

We believe your private information should be just that, private. Clearly, to operate our services we need to collect some personal information about you. This policy explains what we do and why we do it. 

‍ **What we collect

‍

**We ask for your name and email address when you signup to our service. This is our primary mechanism to identify you when you log in. 

‍ **How we store the information

‍

**We take great care to keep your personal information safe, Quuu and its databases operate within the [Amazon Web Services RDS ](https://aws.amazon.com/rds/?sc_channel=PS&sc_campaign=acquisition_UK&sc_publisher=google&sc_medium=rds_b&sc_content=rds_bmm&sc_detail=%2Baws%20%2Brds&sc_category=rds&sc_segment=186498366445&sc_matchtype=b&sc_country=UK&s_kwcid=AL!4422!3!186498366445!b!!g!!%2Baws%20%2Brds&ef_id=VyjAOQAABXZvfJyL:20180420101125:s)platform.

Their computers that are housed in secure data centres with heavily restricted access with numerous levels of security to prevent unauthorised access to those servers including firewalls and passwords.[Amazon provide comprehensive details on RDS Security and Privacy here](https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/UserGuide/UsingWithRDS.html).

‍ **What we do with the information

‍

**Email is a vital part of Quuu, emails are used to communicate new content suggestions and latest news regarding the service. We also use email to send occasional alerts, reminders and newsletters in relation to Quuu and how you use Quuu, all these emails contain a link that allows a user to opt out of further communication with a single click.

The primary use of the data we collect is to provide the Quuu service and to educate the User to help them be more successful. 

‍ **Who we share the information with

‍

**To help us deliver Quuu we use various 3rd party apps. We asses all these apps to ensure compliance with the Data Protection act, our Privacy Policy, and to ensure your data remains in safe hands.

A separate article covering apps we share data with is available here.‍

‍ **Retention and Destruction

‍

**Our policy is to provide our customers with control over retention and destruction of their data. Individual users of Quuu can be deleted anytime. Deletion is instant and irrecoverable. Any data stored on backups will be deleted entirely within 14 days. We will automatically delete user information if user has unsubscribed from emails and after 3 months of application inactivity.

‍ **What we don’t and won’t ever do

‍

**We don’t, and never will sell or rent your information to any 3rd party.

‍ **Updates to this policy

‍

**We update this privacy policy from time-to-time, particularly as technology changes and as Quuu develops. We suggest you check back from time to time for the latest version.
